Colleen Kornblum

React.js & Vue.js Developer

colleendIgd@gmail.com (971)249-2088 2094 Reserve St Plevna, ON K0H 2M0

WORK EXPERIENCE

Rarify

React & Vue Developer

New York City, New York | May 2020 - 2022

- Designed & developed using HTML5, CSS3, EXT JS, Javascript, XML, ReactJS, NodeJS, JSP, JSON, VUEJS, JSF, j2EE and Ajax.
- Developed user interfaces using AJAX, JavaScript, JSON, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Developed dynamic responsive Web Application by intergrating React.js with Bootstrap which is further integrated with Web Services and Vue.js
- Developed application as Enterprise Javascript using Reactjs, Nodejs, Websockets, Jasmine, Karma, NPM, Gulp, Protractor etc.

Bentley University

Frontend Developer

Waltham, Massachusetts, United States | Apr 2018 - Apr 2020

- Implemented ReactJS to create a dynamically changing website.
- Introduced wider use of isomorphic React and Node.js for web applications, decreasing load times by roughly 35%.
- Use of ReactJS help to refresh the pages and update and changed parts.
- Designed Frontend with object oriented javaScript Framework like ReactJS/Redux, NodeJS, Backbone.js, Knockout.js, Spine.js, Ember.js, Require.js, Express.js and Experience with client side templating like Handlebars.js.

Prove (formerly Payfone)

Full-stack Developer

Miami Beach, Florida, United States | Jan 2014 - Mar 2018

- Designed dynamic and browser compatible pages using React, Redux, Html, CSS(Sass), flex, Babel, Sagas.
- Worked multiple components for different course element players and quiz question players using Vue.js and Vuex.
- Developed web applications running on NodeJS using the Express framework, Vue.js and Backbone.js with Mustache.js for front end MVC/templating.

SUMMARY

Experienced Frontend
Developer with 8 years in the industry. Proficient with React, Vue.js. Used problem-solving aptitude to enhance application performance by 14%. Created data visualization tools and integrated designs. Increased speed of product lifecycle and 100% of the time delivered projects within deadline.

SKILLS

- React fundamentals (JSX, Virtual DOM, Native, Node.js)
- Vue.js, Vuex
- CI/CD & DevOps
- CSS, Git, Sigma
- Excellent Communicator
- Flux/Redux
- Team-oriented
- SEO Integration
- Go & Node.js
- GraphQL, Rest API
- gRPC
- Cryptography
- Swagger
- MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Redis
- Elasticsearch
- Apache Kafka
- SQS, SNS
- Docker, Kubernetes
- Microservice
- AWS
- GCP
- Javascript, TypeScript

• Serverless Framework

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree
Computer Science
Nagoya University
Apr 2009 - Aug 2013